ACTWU's Legal Department Records 5619/017
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- General Executive Board Meeting [Part 1 of 13], 1987 (Box 147, Folder 13)
  January 19th to the 23rd. Concerning the termination of the administratorship of the Texas Joint Board and Glove Cities Areas Joint Board, hearing on the continuation of the South Jersey joint board, charges against Nicholas DiPiero, and status reports on administratorhips.
- General Executive Board Meeting [Part 2 of 13], 1987 (Box 147, Folder 14)
  May 18th to the 21st. Concerning the termination of the Philadelphia Joint Board, officer's hearings, and status reports.
- General Executive Board Meeting [Part 3 of 13], 1988 (Box 147, Folder 15)
  February 22nd to the 26th. Memorandums, status reports, and interim actions.
- General Executive Board Meeting [Part 4 of 13], 1987 (Box 147, Folder 16)
  July 29th to the 30th. Hearing officers' report concerning Catawba Valley Joint Board and the continuation of the administratorship of Capmakers Local 4H, and status reports.
- General Executive Board Meeting [Part 5 of 13], 1987 (Box 147, Folder 17)
  March 9th and 10th. Concerning the terminations of the administratorship of the Rochester Joint Board and the appeal of officers from the Northern North Carolina Joint Board, Eden, and North Carolina. Includes status reports.
- General Executive Board Meeting [Part 6 of 13], 1987 (Box 147, Folder 18)
  October 29th to November 1st. Concerning the administratorship of the Texas Joint Board and the Capmaker's Union, Local 4H. Includes status reports and memorandums.
- General Executive Board Meeting [Part 7 of 13], 1988 (Box 147, Folder 19)
  May 2nd to the 4th. Concerning administratorship.
- General Executive Board Meeting [Part 8 of 13], 1988 (Box 147, Folder 20)
  November 29th to the 30th. Concerning the termination of administratorship and an election complaint. Includes agendas and status reports.
- General Executive Board Meeting [Part 9 of 13], 1989 (Box 147, Folder 21)
  January 30th to February 3rd. Requests to submit additions to the agenda.
- General Executive Board Meeting [Part 10 of 13], 1989 (Box 147, Folder 22)
  May 15th to the 19th. Request to submit additions to agenda.
- General Executive Board Meeting [Part 11 of 13], 1989 (Box 147, Folder 23)
  September 5th to the 8th. Concerning the termination of the administratorship for Local 335 in Chicago, Illinois.
- General Executive Board Meeting [Part 12 of 13], 1989 (Box 147, Folder 24)
  November 16th to the 18th. Concerning the Pennsylvania Joint Board and the Scranton and Wilkes Barre District Joint Board to hold Joint Boards semi-annually.
- General Executive Board Meeting [Part 13 of 13], 1990 (Box 147, Folder 25)
  May 7th to the 9th. Hearing Officer's Report concerning Local 1374, Chicago Joint Board.
- Philadelphia Joint Board DiPiero Charges, 1987 (Box 147, Folder 26)
- ACTWU Charges Against James Jackson Example File, 1986 (Box 147, Folder 27)
- Philadelphia Joint Board DiPiero Charge Duplicate File, 1986-1987 (Box 147, Folder 28)
- LM-15, Items Request for Reason to Continue Administratorship, 1986-1989 (Box 147, Folder 29)
- Charges filed against Local 2H officers- Jack Glass & Mariam Bonilla, 1988 (Box 147, Folder 30)
- Termination of Administratorship, 1987-1989 (Box 147, Folder 31)
- Appeal by Loretta Carey et al. Local 2370T, 1989-1990 (Box 147, Folder 32)
- Termination of Administratorship Local 2H, 1987-1988 (Box 147, Folder 33)
- Administratorship Philadelphia Joint Board Clothing Division, 1985-1989 (Box 148, Folder 1)
- Local 253 Columbia, SC Administratorship, 1986-1988 (Box 148, Folder 2)
- Administratorship Local 1226 Ballot Returns, 1988 (Box 148, Folder 3)
- Cemetery Workers, 1989-1990 (Box 148, Folder 4)
- Cemetery Workers, 1989-1990 (Box 148, Folder 5)
- Cemetery Workers Letters and Memos, 1988-1990 (Box 148, Folder 6)
- Cemetery Workers Letters to Mahony, 1990 (Box 149, Folder 1)
- Cemetery Workers Legal, 1990 (Box 149, Folder 2)
- Cemetery Workers Spanish, 1988 (Box 149, Folder 3)
- Cemetery Workers Resolution, Letters, and Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 149, Folder 4)
- Cemetery Workers Rosenberg Depo Materials, 1989-1990 (Box 149, Folder 5)
- Merger ACTWU & ILGWU Original Signed Agreement, 1995 (Box 149, Folder 6)
- Post-Merger Materials, 1995 (Box 149, Folder 7)
- Post Merger/ Merger Material, 1995 (Box 149, Folder 8)
- ACTWU & ILGWU Merger Press Clips, 1995 (Box 149, Folder 9)
- Merger Agreement Drafts, 1995 (Box 149, Folder 10)
- Merger- ACTWU and ILGWU [folder 1 of 2], 1995 (Box 149, Folder 11)
- Merger- ACTWU and ILGWU [folder 1 of 2], 1995 (Box 149, Folder 12)
- Merger (ACTWU & ILGWU) General Correspondence, 1995 (Box 149, Folder 13)
- ACTWU and ILGWU Merger Financial Statements, 1995 (Box 150, Folder 1)
- ACTWU and ILGWU Constitution, 1995 (Box 150, Folder 2)
- ILGWU Convention Call & Delegates Merger Documents, 1995 (Box 150, Folder 3)
- ACTWU & ILGWU Unite Constitution Final, 1995 (Box 150, Folder 4)
- ACTWU & ILGWU Merger Election of Officers, 1993-1994 (Box 150, Folder 5)
- ACTWU & ILGWU Merger- General, 1995 (Box 150, Folder 6)
- Merger (Constitutions) ACWA, TWUA, ACTWU, 1974-1993 (Box 150, Folder 7)
- Shutzer-Barry, 1971-1973 (Box 150, Folder 8)
- Rutter-Rex Brief of Counsel, 1964 (Box 150, Folder 9)
- Prepmore Apparel Co. NLRB File and All Negotiations with Company, 1967 (Box 150, Folder 10)
- Prepmore Apparel Company, Inc. Civil Rights Suit Interrogatories, 1967-1968 (Box 150, Folder 11)
- Prepmore Apparel Company, Inc. Russel Suit, 1971-1972 (Box 150, Folder 12)
- Prepmore Apparel Company, Inc., 1971 (Box 150, Folder 13)
- Prepmore Apparel Company, Inc. 303 Counterclaim, 1970 (Box 150, Folder 14)
- Prepmore Apparel, 1968 (Box 151, Folder 1)
- Prepmore Apparel Company, Inc. Trial Preparations, 1967 (Box 151, Folder 2)
- Prepmore Apparel Co. NLRB File, 1966-1967 (Box 151, Folder 3)
  May 1966 thru May 1967
- Prepmore Apparel Co., Inc. 303 Interrogatories, 1967 (Box 151, Folder 4)
- Prepmore Apparel Co., Inc. Contempt, 1968-1970 (Box 151, Folder 5)
- Thompson Committee Hearings [folder 1 of 4], 1966-1967 (Box 151, Folder 6)
- Thompson Committee Hearings [folder 2 of 4], 1966-1968 (Box 151, Folder 7)
- Thompson Committee Hearings [folder 3 of 4], 1968 (Box 151, Folder 8)
- Thompson Committee Hearings [folder 4 of 4], 1968-1972 (Box 151, Folder 9)
- Thompson Committee Hearing File Anti-Union Material, 1968-1969 (Box 151, Folder 10)